ipinfo.info 2019-08-02

# Privacy Statement

We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Personal data are collected on this website only in the strictly necessary technical and organizational scope. In no event will the data collected be sold or otherwise disclosed to third parties, except as required for prosecution, defense against vandalism or a legally binding obligation.

The following statement gives you an overview of what type of data is collected for what purpose and how we ensure that protection.

### Data processing on this website

As usual, our web server stores information in its log files, which your web browser automatically sends to us when surfing. These include:

  * Browser type and version
  * Operating system used
  * Referer URL (the previously visited page)
  * IP address and host name of the accessing PC
  * Time of the server request

This data can not be assigned to you directly as a person, but only to your Internet connection and web browser type. We store them because these data are used for statistical purposes, such as analysis of which services are particularly strong or low in demand, and are important for the defense against vandalism and malicious server attacks. A merge of this data with other data sources will not be done.

Here you can test online what information your web browser at this moment in total tells our, or other web server: Browsercheck...

### Cookies

The websites use so-called cookies in several places. They serve to make our offer more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small text files that the web browser stores on your computer. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies". They are automatically deleted after your visit. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain viruses. Every common web browser has a function to delete these cookies.  

### Data submitted by you

By sending us information via the webmail form or otherwise, you agree that we may use and share this information with your personal information for the purpose intended, such as answering and tracking your request. We may save this information permanently.

### Newsletter

If you would like to subscribe to a newsletter, we need a valid email address from you, as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified email address or that its owner agrees to receive the newsletter. Further data is not collected. Your consent to the storage of the data, the email address and their use for sending the newsletter, you can revoke at any time.

### Embedded content from other websites

This site may contain embedded content (eg videos, pictures, posts, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behave just as if the visitor had visited the other website. These websites may collect personal information, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking services, and record all interaction with this embedded content.

This website uses Google AdSense. It is a service of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, for the inclusion of advertisements. Google AdSense uses cookies. These are files that the PC Google can use to analyze the data of your use of our website. In addition, Google AdSense uses additional web beacons, invisible graphics that allow Google to analyze clicks on this site, traffic on it and similar information.

The information obtained via cookies and web beacons, your IP address and the delivery of advertising formats are transmitted to and stored by Google on a server located in the USA. Google may share this information with third parties, if required by law or if Google commissions data processing to third parties. However, Google will merge your IP address with the other stored data.

With the appropriate settings on your Internet browser you can prevent the mentioned cookies from being stored on your PC. However, there is the possibility that the contents of this website can no longer be used to the same extent. By using this site, you consent to the processing of personal data by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

### How we protect personal information

All data is stored on a web server in a data center within Germany. This server is constantly monitored and protected against external access by a firewall. Regular updates and patches ensure the greatest possible protection against misuse and malicious attacks. Data breaches can be reported at the contact address stated in the imprint.

### Right to be informed

At any time you have the right to be informed about the data stored in relation to your person, their origin and recipient as well as the purpose of the storage via the contact address stated in the imprint.

To the [imprint of this website ...](https://geotek.de/cms/en/contact_en/contact-impressum_en)
